# Serkan Angün

### **Frontend Developer**

#### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Email: angun.serkan2@gmail.com

Address: Izmir Turkey Phone: +905454963550 Date of birth: Apr, 1996 Nationality: Turkish

Link: https://github.com/angun2serkan

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Jr. Software Developer who has Civil Engineering background. After graduating from Civil Engineering, he worked as a civil engineer for a while. But after realizing that this lifestyle did not suit him, he thought about what he wanted to do and decided to become a software developer. After Full-Stack .NET Developer Bootcamp started as a Frontend Developer Trainee in Bilge Adam Teknolji. At the end of internship started to as a Full-Stack Developer at Ecospend. He loved Frontend development by the time he gained during his working period. Has impressive learning curve, laser focus and suitable character for teamwork

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Izmir, Turkey Jun 2022 - Present

#### **Full Stack Developer**

Ecospend

- Involved in Software Development Life Cycle like Requirement Analisis, Design, Development and Testing.
- Designed and developed the documentation page of company. Used vanillia Javascript and CSS.
- Developed features to business logic for Open Banking Projects. Using C#, .NET.
- Using Web API as an ideal platform in building Restful applications on .NET Framework as backend along
  with the Entity Framework and LINQ to access the databases
- Frontend developments in interfaces of projects. Using ReactJS, Javascript, CSS3, Sass as a preprocessor.
- Deployed the features that is developed into the Azure.

Ankara, Turkey
Mar 2022 - May 2022

## **Fronend Developer Trainee**

Bilge Adam Teknoloji

- After a Bootcamp Program started as a Frontend Developer Trainee
- Developed fully responsive Single Page Applications that designed by design team. Used Html5, CSS3, Javascript
- · Developed React JS components.

# **EDUCATION**

**Izmir, Turkey** 

Oct 2015 - Jun 2020

**Civil Engineering** 

Ege University

Izmir, Turkey

Sep 2021 - Present

**Data Science** 

Dokuz Eylül University

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Advanced

Turkish Native SKILLS

**Teamwork** 

C# HTML

**Javascript** 

Web API LINQ **Asp.NET MVC** 

SQL CSS

React JS

Entity Framework

Sass preprocessor

# REFERENCES



Yiğit Hacıefendioğlu Software Trainer and Team Lead at Bilge Adam:

- Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/yi%C4%9Fit-hac%C4%B1efendio%C4%9Flu-323b1612/
- Email: yigith1gmail.com
- Mobile: +905058395568